

Krasneho 1341/67, Brno, Czech Republic

□ (+420) 732 772 904 | ☑ jirka.kopecky@outlook.com | ☑ jirikopecky | 🛅 jiri-kopecky



## Summary\_

Software developer at Honeywell. 5+ years experience developing server and cloud solutions for connected devices. Nerd who loves to learn about new tools and services, mainly from the .NET world. Out of work loves to play computer games and to read good Sci-Fi or Fantasy book.

# Work Experience

Honeywell - HTS CZ Brno, Czech Republic

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER

- May 2013 PRESENT
- Co-designed architecture of several IoT Cloud solutions
- Designed and implemented multiple microservices in C# targeting Microsoft Service Fabric
- · Designed and implemented CI/CD pipeline using PowerShell scripts, Atlassian Bamboo and Octopus deployment server
- · Deployed a centralized logging environment (ElasticSearch, Kibana) which gather log data from microservices.

Honeywell - HTS CZ Brno, Czech Republic

TECHNICAL SUPPORT / INTERNSHIP

Apr. 2012 - Apr. 2013

· Support of engineering team that developed IoT services

Blue Pixel Solutions a.s. Brno, Czech Republic

C# DEVELOPER / INTERNSHIP

• Development of desktop and web applications in C#

Aug. 2008 - Apr. 2010

## Presentation\_

**Microsoft Build 2018** Seattle, WA

PRESENTER FOR <HOW HONEYWELL MIGRATED THEIR SMART THERMOSTAT APPLICATION TO SERVICE FABRIC>

May 2018

- Summarized how Honeywell Homes Cloud team migrated their solution from Azure Cloud Services to Microsoft Service Fabric
- Available on YouTube: https://youtu.be/VTH2XnMSZ2o

ŽijemelT Brno, Czech Republic

PRESENTER FOR < DEPLOYMENT AUTOMATION IN AZURE>

Feb. 2018

- Small Czech conference intended for students, held at Faculty of Information Technology, Brno University of Technology
- Introduced different ways how to automate code deployment to Microsoft Azure

### Education

## Brno University of Technology, Faculty of Information Technology

Brno, Czech Republic

**BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY** Sep. 2008 - Jun. 2012

#### Certifications

MICROSOFT EXAMS

- 532: Developing Microsoft Azure Solutions
- 483: Programming in C#

#### Skills

JUNE 28, 2018

**Programming** C#, .NET, .NET Core, PowerShell, TypeScript, JavaScript

Cloud Service Fabric, Docker, Microsoft Azure (IoT Hub, Event Hubs, Azure Active Directory)

Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Git Tools

Web React, Redux, HTML5, CSS

Languages Czech, English

JIRI KOPECKY · RÉSUMÉ